A_
A _
A r_
A re_
A rea_
A real_
A real _
A real s_
A real sc_
A real sch_
A real sche_
A real sched_
A real schedu_
A real schedul_
A real schedule_
A real schedule._
A real schedule.
_
H_
A real schedule.
He_
Hea_
A real schedule.
Heal_
Healt_
A real schedule.
Health_
Health _
A real schedule.
Health s_
Health sc_
A real schedule.
Health sco_
Health scor_
A real schedule.
Health score_
Health score:_
A real schedule.
Health score: _
Health score: 5_
A real schedule.
Health score: 50_
Health score: 50 _
A real schedule.
Health score: 50 o_
Health score: 50 ou_
A real schedule.
Health score: 50 out_
Health score: 50 out _
A real schedule.
Health score: 50 out o_
Health score: 50 out of_
A real schedule.
Health score: 50 out of _
Health score: 50 out of 1_
A real schedule.
Health score: 50 out of 10_
Health score: 50 out of 100_
A real schedule.
Health score: 50 out of 100.
P_
Pl_
Pla_
Plan_
Plann_
Planne_
Planned_
Planned _
Planned p_
Planned pr_
Planned pro_
Planned prog_
Planned progr_
Planned progre_
Planned progres_
Planned progress_
Planned progress:_
Planned progress: _
Planned progress: 9_
Planned progress: 90_
Planned progress: 90._
Planned progress: 90.5_
Planned progress: 90.5%_
Planned progress: 90.5%._
Planned progress: 90.5%. _
Planned progress: 90.5%. A_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Ac_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Act_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actu_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actua_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual:_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: _
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 5_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54._
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1%_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1%._
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1%.
_
S_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1%.
SP_
SPI_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1%.
SPI _
SPI 0_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1%.
SPI 0._
SPI 0.6_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1%.
SPI 0.60_
SPI 0.60 _
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1%.
SPI 0.60 -_
SPI 0.60 --_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1%.
SPI 0.60 -- _
SPI 0.60 -- a_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1%.
SPI 0.60 -- al_
SPI 0.60 -- alr_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1%.
SPI 0.60 -- alre_
SPI 0.60 -- alrea_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1%.
SPI 0.60 -- alread_
SPI 0.60 -- already_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1%.
SPI 0.60 -- already _
SPI 0.60 -- already b_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1%.
SPI 0.60 -- already be_
SPI 0.60 -- already beh_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1%.
SPI 0.60 -- already behi_
SPI 0.60 -- already behin_
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1%.
SPI 0.60 -- already behind_
SPI 0.60 -- already behind.
Planned progress: 90.5%. Actual: 54.1%.
O_
Or_
Ord_
Ordo_
Ordo7_
Ordo7 _
Ordo7 d_
Ordo7 do_
Ordo7 doe_
Ordo7 does_
Ordo7 doesn_
Ordo7 doesn'_
Ordo7 doesn't_
Ordo7 doesn't _
Ordo7 doesn't s_
Ordo7 doesn't st_
Ordo7 doesn't sto_
Ordo7 doesn't stop_
Ordo7 doesn't stop _
Ordo7 doesn't stop a_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at _
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a _
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a s_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a sc_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a sco_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a scor_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score _
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score -_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
_
i_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it_
it _
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it f_
it fo_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it for_
it fore_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it forec_
it foreca_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it forecas_
it forecast_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it forecasts_
it forecasts _
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it forecasts t_
it forecasts th_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it forecasts the_
it forecasts the _
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it forecasts the f_
it forecasts the fi_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it forecasts the fin_
it forecasts the fini_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it forecasts the finis_
it forecasts the finish_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it forecasts the finish _
it forecasts the finish d_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it forecasts the finish da_
it forecasts the finish dat_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it forecasts the finish date_
it forecasts the finish date _
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it forecasts the finish date t_
it forecasts the finish date tw_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it forecasts the finish date two_
it forecasts the finish date two _
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it forecasts the finish date two w_
it forecasts the finish date two wa_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it forecasts the finish date two way_
it forecasts the finish date two ways_
Ordo7 doesn't stop at a score --
it forecasts the finish date two ways.
A_
At_
At _
At c_
At cu_
At cur_
At curr_
At curre_
At curren_
At current_
At current _
At current p_
At current pa_
At current pac_
At current pace_
At current pace:_
At current pace: _
At current pace: J_
At current pace: Ja_
At current pace: Jan_
At current pace: Jan _
At current pace: Jan 2_
At current pace: Jan 20_
At current pace: Jan 202_
At current pace: Jan 2027_
At current pace: Jan 2027._
At current pace: Jan 2027.
_
B_
At current pace: Jan 2027.
Ba_
Bac_
At current pace: Jan 2027.
Back_
Back _
At current pace: Jan 2027.
Back o_
Back on_
At current pace: Jan 2027.
Back on _
Back on p_
At current pace: Jan 2027.
Back on pl_
Back on pla_
At current pace: Jan 2027.
Back on plan_
Back on plan:_
At current pace: Jan 2027.
Back on plan: _
Back on plan: N_
At current pace: Jan 2027.
Back on plan: No_
Back on plan: Nov_
At current pace: Jan 2027.
Back on plan: Nov _
Back on plan: Nov 2_
At current pace: Jan 2027.
Back on plan: Nov 20_
Back on plan: Nov 202_
At current pace: Jan 2027.
Back on plan: Nov 2026_
Back on plan: Nov 2026._
At current pace: Jan 2027.
Back on plan: Nov 2026. _
Back on plan: Nov 2026. Y_
At current pace: Jan 2027.
Back on plan: Nov 2026. Yo_
Back on plan: Nov 2026. You_
At current pace: Jan 2027.
Back on plan: Nov 2026. Your_
Back on plan: Nov 2026. Your _
At current pace: Jan 2027.
Back on plan: Nov 2026. Your c_
Back on plan: Nov 2026. Your ca_
At current pace: Jan 2027.
Back on plan: Nov 2026. Your cal_
Back on plan: Nov 2026. Your call_
At current pace: Jan 2027.
Back on plan: Nov 2026. Your call?